前情提要
Previously on Class of '09...
在这里 我们会彼此握手
Out here, we shake each other's hands.
（现在）
先生 我不是来买牛的
Well, I'm not here to buy a cow, sir.
-值得吗  -他们自己暴露了
Was it worth it? They revealed themselves.
去你的
Fuck you!
-他们计画攻击的目标是什么  -我们
What are they planning to attack? Us.
我可以看清楚 你听到消息时脸上的表情
I get to see the expression on your face when you hear the news.
有些逮捕行动理由不明
There are inexplicable arrests.
（未来）
-你知 我知 -不 参议员 我不知道
You know it, I know it. No, Senator, I don't know it.
波伊特探员 你一直被蒙蔽
Special Agent Poet, you've been lied to.
这个系统会自己建立连结
This system is making connections on its own.
这是跟我们截然不同的智慧
This is an intelligence nothing like our own.
联邦凶杀案
第一季第四集
本WEB版外挂字幕由  风吹来的那片云  双语合并
（过去 1996年）
-嫌犯要进入公寓了 -收到
Suspect is entering the apartment. Copy.
嫌犯自己一个人 没看到他的女友
Suspect is alone. No sign of his girlfriend.
收到 准备进去
Copy. Moving in.
-联调局 开门 -开门
FBI. Open up. Open up!
手举起来 趴下 快点 趴下
Hands up! Get down! Gun! Stay on him!
我们应该待在车内
We should stay in the van.
去抓他 快点
Get off me.
可恶 放开我
Get him, let's go.
放开我
Hold him down.
联调局 不要动
FBI! Stop right there!
该死 茱儿…
Oh, shit. Drew. Drew.
她应该要待在车内的
She was supposed to stay in the van.
她为什么会在这里  她到底在这里做什么
Why was she there? What the hell was she doing?
撑着点
Hang in there.
这是我当探员的第一把手枪 西格绍尔P228
This was my weapon as an agent. A SIG Sauer p228.
你开过枪吗 长官  我是说在出任务时
Did you ever fire it, ma'am? On duty, I mean.
没有 我从未开过枪
No, I never did.
调查局第一把制式武器 是四吋枪管的柯特警用左轮
The Bureau's first official weapon. A four-inch barreled Colt Police revolver.
在1934年发给毕业班学员
Issued to the class of 1934 at graduation.
我们现在使用的主要武器是克拉克23
Today the primary weapon we use is the Glock 23.
这把叫做红把手
This one is called the red handle
因为枪管塞住 撞针也移除了
because the barrel has been blocked and the firing pin removed.
训练期间 你们在基地要带着这把枪
During your training, you will carry these around the base.
目的是要你们熟悉它的重量
We want you to get accustomed to the weight of them.
触感 以及概念
The feel of them. The idea of them.
长官 概念是指什么
The idea of them, ma'am?
取人性命意谓着什么
What it means to take a life.
冒着自己的生命危险意谓着什么
What it means to risk your life.
除非想要开枪 否则探员不会拔枪
A special agent doesn't draw their gun unless they intend to fire.
如果你觉得自己无法取人性命 那你就当不成探员
If you decide that you cannot take a life, you cannot be a special agent.
当你拿到武器 请跟班上同学说一下
When you receive your weapon, I'd like you to tell the class
自己在枪枝方面的经验
about your own experiences with firearms.
你对枪很熟门熟路
You know your way around a gun.
我成年之后就常跑靶场 长官
I spent most of my adult life in a shooting range, sir.
那是什么样的靶场
What's the story of this range?
芝加哥枪枝学院 长官 由一对和善的越南夫妇所经营
Chicago Gun Academy, sir. Ran by a lovely Vietnamese couple.
去那里的人不是想要拿枪射谁
The people going there weren't dreaming of shooting anybody,
他们只是不想被人开枪
they just didn't want to be shot.
这是我第一次拿枪
This is the first time I've ever held a gun.
你何时提出申请的
When did you apply?
六个月前
Six months ago.
如果你们不接受 我说出来也没什么意义
There wasn't any point in telling you if I wasn't going to be accepted.
你没有告诉我们 是因为你知道我们会说不
You didn't tell us because you knew we'd say no.
为什么现在要告诉我们
Why tell us now?
下一阶段是测谎 如果我没有告诉你们
The next stage is the polygraph. So if I hadn't told you...
-那可能会出现在我的答案里 -乌尔 你在做什么
maybe it would show up in my answers. Hour. What are you doing?
-你有麻省理工的学位 -他们喜欢我这点
You have a degree from MIT. They like that about me.
因为没有其他人 会这样浪费自己的教育背景
Because nobody else would waste their education in this way.
这是你一无所知的世界
This is not a world you know anything about.
我们搭地铁上班 这样才不会在开车时被拦下来
We take the Metro to work so we won't be stopped in our car.
我们度假时是搭车 这样才不会在机场被拦下来
We take the car on vacation so we won't be stopped at the airports.
我不想要这样的生活
I don't want to live that way.
-我想要有归属感 -这是你选择的生活
I want to feel part of something. And this is what you choose?
-他们需要我 爸 -但你为什么需要他们
They want me, Dad. But why do you want them?
他们会叫你做什么
What will they have you do?
-监视自己的同胞  -爸爸 这又不是秘密警察
Spy on your own people? Baba, this isn't the secret police.
他们一定会对我们家进行背景调查
They must have carried out a background check on our family.
-你把他们带进了我们的生活 -我们没什么好隐瞒的
You've brought them into our lives. We have nothing to hide.
那不是重点 那从来就不是重点
That doesn't matter. That has never mattered.
你在生我们的气吗
Are you angry with us?
这是跟…
Is this about...
-其他事情有关吗  -那会是什么 妈妈
something else? What might it be about, Mom?
你是…
You were...
孤独的孩子
a lonely child.
或许你现在还是很孤独
Perhaps you're lonely still.
或许我会一直孤独下去
Maybe I'll always be lonely.
想要在这个国家有归属感有其他方法
There are other ways to feel a part of this country.
想要跟我们有不同感受也有其他方法
And other ways to feel different from us.
希望你们以我为荣 是不是太过奢求了
Was it too much to hope that you'd be proud of me?
请抬起手臂
Would you lift your arms, please?
-我可以自己来 -不行 得由我来
- I can do that. - No, it has to be me.
请把手摊平
Will you lay your hands flat, please?
可以解释一下你正在做什么吗
Could you explain what you're doing?
从来没有人问过
Nobody ever asks that.
椅子上有侦测动作的感测器
There's a sensor in the chair that detects movement.
这些是测量你呼吸频率的列线图管
These are pneumography tubes, measure your rate of respiration.
这些会测量你的肤电活动 那个会量血压
These measure electrodermal activity. That's for your blood pressure.
测试大概要花两个小时
The test will take approximately two hours.
如果你的答案没有反应 可能会花上四小时
And if your answers are unresponsive, it can take up to four.
你的答案只能局限在是与否
You have to limit your answers to yes or no.
你随时可以终止测试 但这样做会造成失败
You can stop the test at any time, but to do so would constitute a fail.
你有权找律师 但这么做会…
And you have the right to an attorney, but to call for one would...
造成失败
Constitute a fail.
会紧张是正常的
It's normal to be nervous.
我不紧张 我是好奇
I'm not nervous. I'm curious.
-谁来解读这些反应  -我
Who interprets the responses? I do.
-你做过多少测试  -几百次
How many tests have you done? Oh, hundreds.
每年有五万人申请加入联邦调查局
There are 50,000 applicants to the Bureau each year.
政府一定执行了几百万次这样的测试
The government must have carried out millions of these tests.
-经年累月 -你们会…
Over the years. Do you...
搜集资料吗
collect the data?
我们会以档案形式保存
We keep 'em on file.
-是存放在集中式资料库吗  -不是
But is it on a centralized database? No.
这些资料如果能交叉比对
Doesn't it make sense to cross-reference them
而非依赖单一个人的解读 不是更合理吗
rather than rely on one person's interpretation?
之前不是有李文和的案子 那个洛沙拉摩斯的核子科学家
There was the case of Wen Ho Lee. Nuclear scientist at Los Alamos
-他被控当中国的间谍 -我知道这个案子
accused of being a Chinese spy? I know the case.
他通过了能源部的测谎 但是当联调局重新检视同一份结果
He passed the DOE polygraph. But the FBI reexamined the same results
他们判定他在说谎
and they decided he was lying.
他把W88小型核弹头的秘密 泄漏给中国
That he had slipped China secrets about the miniaturized W88 warhead.
如果你们把搜集到的资料 都放到集中式资料库
Maybe if you collated all the data on a central database,
或许判读就不会那么主观了
it wouldn't be so subjective.
你知道 有些人不想要通过测试
You know, some people want to fail a test.
他们会故意采取某种方式 让自己退出流程
They deliberately flunk it in a way to drop out of the process
却又不会丢脸 如果你是这种情况 尽管说
without losing face. If that's you, just say so.
可以开始了吗
Can we begin?
（现在 2023年）
真遗憾先前没有握手
Excuse me for not shaking your hand.
-一名海军陆战队员曾经跟我说… -抱歉 这名海军陆战队员
Marine once told me... I'm sorry, this Marine,
是你的朋友还是…
is he a friend of yours, or...?
朋友 好朋友 爱国者
Friend. Close friend. Patriot.
他说一个人在第一次杀人之后
He said after a man kills for the first time,
他的皮肤味道会改变
the smell of his skin changes.
你的妻子
Your wife.
她是你杀的第一个人吗
Was she the first person you've killed?
我把她从破烂的地方救出来
Well, I rescued her from squalor.
修补她的牙齿 整理她的头发
I fixed her teeth, her hair.
照顾她生存的一切所需
Overlooked everything she had to do to survive.
听起来你照顾过头了
Yeah, sounds like you overlooked quite a bit
因为你看不出来她恨你
because you couldn't see that she hated you.
那你的太太呢
What about your wife?
看起来我让你们两个人都成了凶手
Looks like I made killers of you both.
我认为可以肯定地说 我们有正当理由 不是吗
I think it's safe to say that we had just cause, wouldn't you?
“正当理由”
Just cause?
Just cause.
你跑到我的牧场就是想要找这个吗
Is that what you were looking for out at my ranch?
“正当理由” 你一辈子都在找正当理由
"Just cause." Yeah, you've been looking for that your whole life.
你有了徽章和枪
And you got your badge and your gun.
现在只需要“正当理由” 就可以为所欲为
All you needed was that "just cause" to get away with it.
为所欲为 是啊
"To get away with it," yeah.
我们来谈谈“为所欲为”
Let's talk about that, "getting away with it."
因为如果能为所欲为 我会去乱逛你的牧场
Because getting away with it, I would've just strolled on your ranch.
我会一枪打中你眉心
And I would've shot you right between the eyes.
也许我应该这么做 因为如此一来你太太就不会丧命
And maybe I should've because then... your wife would still be alive.
我的搭档不会躺在医院床上
My partner wouldn't be lying in a hospital bed.
我太太也不会遭受攻击 但我没有
And my wife wouldn't have been attacked. But I didn't.
不…我没有
No, no, no, I didn't.
你是蒙大拿阶级最高的联调局探员
You're the highest ranking FBI agent in Montana.
如果不是猎捕像我这样的人 你在例行的外勤工作当中
What you doing on a routine piece of fieldwork
还能做什么
if not hunting for folks like me?
没错 你已经梦想这天好几年了
Yeah, you've been dreaming of that day for years.
让我们把事情说清楚
Let's... Let's be very clear about something.
你可能有很多身分
You may be many things,
但你绝对不是我的梦想
but you are no dream of mine.
我们搞清楚了他们被逮时
Have we figured out where they were driving to
-正要开车去哪里吗  -我们无法理解他们的路线
when they were caught? We can't make sense of their route.
（计算可能目的地）
有没有可能他们在声东击西
Is it possible that they were a diversion?
为了避开什么
A diversion from what?
表现不错 乌尔 你是天生好手
Nice job, Hour. You're a natural.
泰约 换你了
Tayo, you're up.
表现得很好…
Nice job.
射手准备
Shooter, stand by.
好枪法 学员
Nice shooting, trainee.
射手 准备
Shooter, stand by.
你为什么僵住了 学员
Why did you freeze, trainee?
不 我没有僵住
Ma'am, I didn't freeze.
你没开枪
You didn't fire.
-我不认为她是威胁 -为什么 她手拿武器
I didn't consider her to be a threat. Why not? She's armed.
但她是谁呢 她是一名女性 看起来是专业人士
But who is she? She's a woman, she looks like a professional,
-我猜她是执法人员 -她拿的不是克拉克
my guess would be law enforcement. She's not holding a Glock.
史密斯威森640 是下班警察可合法配戴的枪
Smith & Wesson 640. Approved for off-duty police officers.
所以你在那电光火石之间 判断她是下班的警探
So you decided in that split second she was an off-duty detective?
他们也用那些枪来保护自己
Well, they also use those guns for personal protection.
她可能是要逃离有暴力倾向的伙伴
She could be escaping a violent partner.
这项测试不是要帮她写传记
The test wasn't to write her biography.
但我们不用吗  如果我们要取她性命的话
But don't we have to, if we're gonna take her life?
-嘿 -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
刚刚我很为你感到骄傲
I was proud of you back there.
你觉得骄傲
You were proud?
-我说错话了 对吧  -没有
Oh, I said the wrong word, didn't I? No.
不管正确的字眼是什么 那是我当时的感受
Well, whatever the, uh, the right word is, that is how I felt.
正确的字眼不是你说了算吗
Isn't it up to you to decide what the right word is?
-你很难恭维 -而且很容易得罪
You're a hard person to compliment. And an easy one to offend?
我没那么说
I didn't say that.
你在哪里学会开枪的
Where'd you learn how to shoot?
我妈 在后院打锡罐
My mom. Tin cans in the backyard.
她认为任何独居的女性 都应该知道怎么开枪
She believed any woman who lived alone should know how to shoot.
-你呢  -我爸…
- You? - My dad.
猎鹿
Hunting deer.
我在做什么
What am I doing?
我应该要工作 而不是去约会
I'm supposed to be working, not going on dates.
-这是心有旁骛 -坠入爱河不是心有旁骛
He's a distraction. Falling in love is not a distraction.
我没有坠入爱河
I'm not in love.
接下来五个月会决定我们的下半辈子
I mean, these next five months decide the rest of our lives.
任何五个月都会决定我们的下半辈子
Any five months decide the rest of our lives.
有些月份就是比较重要
Well, some months are more important than others.
中学时我有朋友都在胡搞瞎搞 现在
I had friends in high school who...
他们有的是时间 但就是无法改变自己的人生
messed around and now they have all the time in the world, but they can't change their lives.
我知道那种感觉 那是内疚
I know these feelings. It's guilt.
我爱上某个人时 也会有这种感觉
I felt the same way when I'd fall for someone.
我没有爱上他 我只是…喜欢他
I haven't fallen for him, I just... I like him.
对我来说 内疚就是…
For me the guilt is...
因为我没有结婚 对你来说 就是职业道德
...because I'm not married. For you it's work ethic.
你知道吗…
Yeah.
我妈从来没有跟任何人约会过
My mom never dated anyone.
我爸离家出走时 她答应我绝不会带男朋友回家
When my dad... walked out, she promised me she'd never bring a boyfriend home.
我一直都没有父亲 所以 她要弥补这一点
I never had a father, so she was gonna make up for that.
但是当我年纪渐长…
But when I got older, you know, and...
并意识到这让她付出了什么代价 我应该要说
and realized what this was costing her, I-I should have said...
“没关系的 你可以去约会
"It's fine, you can date.
你不必是孤单一人”
You don't have to be alone."
也许如果我…
Maybe if I had...
没关系的 你可以去约会 你不必是孤单孤单一人
It's fine. You can date. You don't have to be alone.
-你可以跟我来吗  -是 长官
Can you come with me, please? Yes, ma'am.
在训练的这个阶段 我们会再次进行测谎
At this point in the training, we repeat your polygraph test
然后比较两次的反应
and compare your responses.
只有我吗
Only me?
为什么会只有你
Why would it only be you?
好的
Right.
想办法放松 我不想要你因为紧张而没过关
Try to relax. I'd hate to fail you because you couldn't relax.
你是否服用过任何非法毒品
Have you ever taken any illegal narcotics?
是
Yes.
你在申请表里填了你曾吸过几次大麻
You listed on your application the occasions you smoked marijuana.
-现在还是只有那几次吗  -是
Are these still the only occasions? Yes.
是在做爱之后抽的吗
Were they after sex?
否
No.
令堂曾经对处方药上瘾吗
Was your mother ever addicted to prescription medication?
是
Yes.
你曾经对处方药上瘾吗
Have you ever been addicted to prescription medication?
否
No.
在这个过程中 你是否隐瞒了任何
You concealed anything during this process
可能会对你的申请 造成负面影响的事情
which might negatively influence your application?
是
Yes.
你先前的答案是“否” 你现在要把它改成“是”
Your previous answer was no. You're changing your answer to yes?
是
Yes.
-你先前说谎吗  -否
Did you lie before? No.
所以是新发生的事
This is something new?
是
Yes.
下一个问题 你可以不用
For the next question, I'm going to release you
只回答“是”与“否”
of the obligation saying yes or no.
你隐瞒了什么事
What have you concealed?
你重新接受过测谎了吗
Have you retaken the polygraph?
上个星期
Last week.
-是吗 结果如何  -一样
Oh, yeah? How'd it go? The same.
你什么话也不跟我说
You didn't say something to me?
要说什么
What's to say?
你有把我们的事情告诉他们吗
Did you tell them about us?
我们的事 没有 你有吗
About us? No. Did you?
他们问我有没有隐瞒任何事
I mean... they asked me if I was concealing anything.
那不是在说我们
They weren't talking about us.
你怎么知道 这违反规定
How do you know? This is against the rules.
-什么规定  -联邦调查局学员守则
What rules? The agent trainee rules.
-你真的读了那种东西  -拜托 这很重要
You actually read those? Come on. This is important.
这里又不是中学
This isn't high school.
所以你觉得 我们不需要让盖布瑞和茱儿知道
So you don't think we need to let Gabriel and Drew know?
-不关他们的事 -每件事都关他们的事
It's none of their business. Everything is their business.
我们的不是
Not us.
-介意我跟你一起走吗  -当然不
Mind if I walk with you? Oh, of course not.
我想要谈谈你的测谎
I wanted to talk about your polygraph.
我没通过吗
Oh, did I fail?
听着 我现在不是 以指导者的身分讲话
Look, I'm not speaking as your supervisor right now.
好
Okay.
自从女性获准加入调查局以来 就一直有绯闻或情侣产生
Ever since women were allowed to join, there have been hookups and couples.
有些人到后来甚至还结了婚 但多数人没有
Some even end up getting married. Most don't.
我不想让你感到尴尬
I'm not trying to embarrass you.
只是想让你察觉我们处境的现实面
I just wanted you to be aware of the reality of our situation.
你是指
Which is...?
如果不顺利 情况变得糟糕的总是女性
If it doesn't work out, the woman always comes off worse.
遭受打击的总是女性
She always takes the hit.
不应该是这样 但现实就是如此
It shouldn't be that way. But it is.
我不是要叫你采取不同的作法
And I'm not telling you to do anything differently.
我只是要告诉你 事情就是这样
I'm telling you the way it is.
我很感激
I appreciate that.
初入职场时 我涉入一起事件 变成了被指责的对象
I was in an incident at the beginning of my career, for which I was blamed.
那是一起探员对探员的枪击事件
It was an agent-on-agent shooting.
-你开枪打探员  -不是 我是挨子弹的那个人
- You shot an agent? - No. I was the one who was shot.
-你说被怪罪的人是你  -没错
You said you were blamed? I was.
他们提出的原因是说我在错误的位置
One of the reasons they gave was they said I was in the wrong place.
但我在的位置跟男性一模一样
And I was in the same place as the guys.
真遗憾
I'm so sorry.
要不是对方的枪法太差 我早就没命了
Ah, I'd be dead if they weren't such lousy shots.
-你为什么还留在局里  -我不能让他们赢
Why did you stay in the Bureau? I couldn't let 'em win.
我是当年度最佳学员
I was one of the best trainees my year.
当我康复 我就回到了教室
So, when I recovered, I just came back to the classroom.
因为…这里是唯一 能让我有所成就的地方
'Cause... that's the only place I was ever allowed to be great.
（未来 2034年）
你好
Hey.
我可以进去吗
Can I come in?
房子很大
Big house.
对 有女孩子在的时候 感觉不错
Yeah, it's nice when the girls stay.
那样的情况有多频繁
How often is that?
不如我想要的那么频繁
Not as often as I'd like.
真遗憾
I'm sorry.
是啊 我也觉得
Yeah, so am I.
我依靠家庭关系想要了解…
I leaned on my family connections to try and see if...
谁是盟友
you know, who was an ally.
很多人…
A lot of people are...
真的很担心这套系统
really worried about this system.
他们认为它太庞大 也太强大
Uh, they think it's too big, it's too powerful.
很多人只会在私底下表达担忧
A lot of people will only express their concerns in private.
没有太多人愿意帮忙
Not a lot are willing to help.
-不令人讶异 对吧  -对
No surprise there, right? No.
光是谈论就可能让人惹上麻烦
Even talking can get people in trouble.
有些人因为我接近他们而感到生气
Some got mad at me for approaching them
-面对面 远离摄影机 -你爸有帮助吗
face-to-face, away from cameras. Is your dad helping?
他认识人面广的人 其中包括史宾塞参议员
He knows people that know people, including Senator Spenser,
所以 我正在设法安排会面
so I'm trying to... set up a meeting.
但就像我说的 人们很害怕
But like I said, people are scared.
我想说的是 在这件事…
I wanted to say that... you know, before this goes too far,
变得不可收拾之前 你不必为了我而一起调查
you don't have to be a part of the investigation into Tayo's system
-泰约的系统 -诗人 别这样
for my sake. Poet, stop.
-你可以自己进行 我懂 -你…
You can do it on your own. I-I get it. You...
你总是认为我喜欢自己一个人
You always had it in your mind that I preferred to be alone.
因为你一向如此
Because you always are.
不是我的话也没关系
If not me, okay.
但至少要有别人
But someone.
我…
Am...
我是问题吗
Am I the problem?
每次感觉不错时 你总是不相信 好像那不会是真的一样
Every time something feels good, you mistrust it. Like it can't be real.
你会不断测试 直到它崩坏
So you test it and you test it until it breaks.
然后你会对自己说 “看吧 我一直都是对的”
And you say to yourself, "You see? I was right all along."
这是我们之间没有成功的原因吗
Is that why we didn't make it?
或许我生命中的每件事 看起来都很轻松
Maybe everything in my life seemed too easy.
而你不想要成为其中一件事
And you wouldn't be another one of those things.
但我现在可以跟你说…
But I can tell you now...
爱上你并不轻松
loving you has not been easy.
而我已经爱你二十年了
And I've loved you for 20 years.
这就是为什么你不应该牵扯进这件事
That is why you should not be involved in this.
诗人 这次不行
Not this time, Poet.
这次你必须告诉我毫无机会
This time, you're gonna have to tell me it doesn't stand a chance.
这次不会是我
This time, it's not gonna be me.
图皮瑞克能让人渗透进局里吗
Could Tupirik have people infiltrate the Bureau?
为什么不呢
Why not?
-一直都有查核 -测谎吗
There are checks. The polygraph?
我测谎时就说谎了
I lied on mine.
你对什么事说谎
What'd you lie about?
只有真正重要的事
Only the really important things.
几个州发起了至少十几次的搜索行动
At least a dozen manhunts
想要逮捕马克图皮瑞克 民兵组织的其他主要成员
for additional key members of Mark Tupirik's militia are underway in multiple states...
目前调查局正试图厘清
as the Bureau attempts to figure out the scope
反政府民兵运动的范围与规模
and scale of his anti-government militia.
枪枝射击评鉴就在今天
Firearms assessment is today.
你有吗
You got it?
谢谢
Thanks.
我们今天行动
We go today.
我要你看一下萤幕上的这些人
at the people on this screen.
你在怕什么
What are you afraid of?
你认为自己很容易就会被…
You think you'll be too easy to read?
像我这样的人看穿
By a man like me?
系统发现情绪紧张的动作
The system is picking up elevated movements,
瞳孔放大 心跳加快
pupil dilation, heart rate increase.
我们找到人了
We've got one.
下一位
Next.
我以前见过这个人
I've seen this man before.
在车库里施工
Doing construction in the garage.
我们认为嫌犯可能就在宽提科
We think the suspect may be at Quantico.
听令 一边向前走 一边射击目标
On the signal, walk forward while shooting at the target.
有人开枪…
Shooter! Shooter!
-嘿 -快逃
Hey!
拜托
No, please!
-她流了好多血 -干得好
She's losing so much blood. You're gonna be all right.
宽提科有警报
There's an alert at Quantico.
-我想请你立刻跟我碰面 -在哪里 这里吗
Hey. I need you to meet me right now. Where? Here?
如果我错了 我来承担 但我们必须疏散这栋大楼
I'll take the heat if I'm wrong, but we need to evacuate this building.
好了 我们走吧
注意…请立刻撤离这栋建筑物
Attention, attention. Please evacuate this building immediately.
这不是演习
This is not a drill.
注意…请立刻撤离这栋建筑物
Attention. Attention. Please evacuate this building immediately.
这不是演习
This is not a drill.
注意…请立刻撤离这栋建筑物
Attention. Attention. Please evacuate this building immediately.
这不是演习
This is not a drill.
嘿
Hey!
好了 换下一根柱子
嘿 不要动
Hey, freeze!
放轻松…我只是要去找我的主管
Easy. Easy. I just got to go get my supervisor.
注意…请立刻撤离这栋建筑物
Hurry! Please evacuate this building immediately.
这不是演习
This is not a drill.
疏散…
我们必须离开 现在就走
We have to go! We have to go now!
（联邦调查局胡佛大楼）
字幕翻译：江霸子